<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learn in 5 on Learn Code Stream</title><link>https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/</link><description>Recent content in Learn in 5 on Learn Code Stream</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding a Kubernetes Endpoint</title><link>https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/adding-a-kubernetes-endpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/adding-a-kubernetes-endpoint/</guid><description>In order to use a Kuberenetes Task , or to use a kubernetes cluster as your pipeline workspace , you need to configure a kubernetes endpoint .
Prerequisites Any Kubernetes compliant cluster Network connectivity to the Kubernetes cluster - either direct or via a Cloud Proxy (for vrealize automation cloud) An authentication token, certificate, or basic authentication username and password</description></item><item><title>Publishing Preserved Artifacts</title><link>https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/publishing-preserved-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/publishing-preserved-artifacts/</guid><description>With the CI task in a Code Stream Pipeline, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to Preserve Artifacts - any file that you want to persist beyond the lifetime of a Pipeline Execution can be added to the Preserve Artifacts field. These preserved artifacts are stored on the Shared Path on the Docker Host , which you can access later using the file path specified in the CI task outputs. One of the issues with this is that the Shared Path is also where the pipeline execution logs are kept, which may contain sensitive information if you&amp;rsquo;re not using Secret Variables , and to deliver a preserved file to an end user you may need to grant SSH access to your host - not ideal.</description></item><item><title>Slack Notifications</title><link>https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/slack-notifications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://learncodestream.github.io/learn-in-5/slack-notifications/</guid><description>Using the webhook function for Pipeline Notifications or Task Notifications and the Slack Incoming Webhooks app it&amp;rsquo;s possible to get a rich set of notifications on pipeline events.
Once your Incoming Webhooks app is configured you will get a URL to post your messages to, and the notification is a simple configuration:
Configure a Slack Notification The Slack payload can be configured as simply, or as complex, as you like:</description></item></channel></rss>